Min Thway Khine



October 27, 1996



+66 379 00 644



minthway.pyae2@gmail.com

SOCIAL MEDIA



in http://linkedin.com/in/min-thway-khine90/

PROFILE

Experienced IT consultant with 8 years of success providing freelance IT solutions, including approximately 2 years of Co-operation leading organizational technology strategy. Adept and knowledgeable at installing and maintaining hardware, software. Trains and oversees dedicated tech team to provide maintenance, troubleshooting and IT support. In another position, Business Operation Manager with around 3years experienced in supporting busy racing Government Electricity Tender. Monitors projects by adhering to production schedule and budget, managing production team, identifying problems and providing targeted solutions.

EDUCATION

06/2019 - 07/2020

BSc(Hons) Business Information Technology

University of Greenwich, UK

01/2015 - 03/2019

Level 5 Diploma in Computing

NCC Education, UK

2018

Cisco Certified Network Associate

BIM Training Center

EXPERIENCE

01/2016 - 03/2024

Freelance IT Solution Service

Personal Enterprise

- Proficient in repairing and replacing computer components including RAM, Hard Disk, and internal parts.
- Knowledgeable in installing and configuring operating systems (Windows, macOS, iOS) and software applications.
- Excellent customer service and communication skills, with a focus on client satisfaction
- Ability to work independently and efficiently manage workload.

05/2023 - 04/2024

IT Project Supervisor

BleuPay

- Handled interactions with external collaborative organizations, gathered data, conducted meetings with team members, and provided reports to the Project Manager.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to identify technology needs and implemented appropriate solutions for improved workflow efficiency.
- Created long-range IT plan to support projected growth and requirements for added capacity.
- Identified computer hardware and software issues, performing troubleshooting techniques for remediation.



11/2022 - 04/2023

Data Entry Officer

CHUBB Insurance

- Manual data input from paper-based sources into the electronic system.
- Check and report to senior associates all the information on the system is accurate and up-to-date.
- Physical data can be systematically organized and examined for any inconsistencies within the system, ensuring alignment with digital data
- Worked closely with IT teams to plan, develop and maintain technical strategies aligned for software.

03/2018 - 02/2021

Business Operation Manager

Myanmar Golden Opportunity Co., Ltd.

- Managed day-to-day business operations and public relations.
- Standardized employee training, improved worker knowledge and increased customer satisfaction.
- Drove year-over-year business growth while leading operations, strategic vision and long-range planning.
- Developed strong relationships with vendors, resulting in better pricing and improved service quality.

07/2017 - 02/2018

IT Technician

AnyMart Co., Ltd.

- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up workstations for employees.
- Set up hardware and software in optimal configurations to meet network performance requirements.
- Investigate and correct problems with printers, copiers and other peripheral devices.
- Help backend developer to troubleshot and test software and debugged to clean up code and improve efficiency.

INTEREST

LANGUAGES

✓ Learning a new skill

Burmese - Native

Maintain and Developing IT devices

English - Intermediate

✓ Leadership and Management skills

SKILLS

- ✓ Self-motivated, with a strong sense of personal responsibility
- ✓ Problem-Solving and Analysis
- ✓ Good Time Management

OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Volunteer Photo Festival in Institute Français 2018
- Volunteer in Yangon International Gems & Jewellery Fair 2018